const universalCounterQuiz = [
  {
    items: [
      {
        id: 'q1',
        question: 'one',
        answer: 'ひとつ　一つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q2',
        question: 'two',
        answer: 'ふたつ　二つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q3',
        question: 'three',
        answer: 'みっつ　三つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q4',
        question: 'four',
        answer: 'よっつ　四つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q5',
        question: 'five',
        answer: 'いつつ　五つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q6',
        question: 'six',
        answer: 'むっつ　六つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q7',
        question: 'seven',
        answer: 'ななつ　七つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q8',
        question: 'eight',
        answer: 'やっつ　八つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q9',
        question: 'nine',
        answer: 'ここのつ　九つ',
      },
      {
        id: 'q10',
        question: 'ten',
        answer: 'とお　十',
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default universalCounterQuiz;

